Give me. Take these ones.
Who is that?
Come on, sisters.
Come on, brothers.
We have to finish this. Work harder.
Come on.
Come on, faster.
Come on, come on.
May your work be easy.
Mother, how can we finish all this?
We have to, dear. Come on.
Come on, faster.
Look at that.
Mother, which soldier can that bread even feed?
Even Ghazi won't be full with that.
Whoever tries hard will find the success, dear.
Our alps are going on a raid.
Who knows when they will be back?
So we have to work much more.
Come on.
Every bread we bake and every meal
we cook will make our soldiers stronger!
Bala Hatun, I'm ready to conquer with the alps!
I know that, my boy.
But we need you here in
the tribe for now, alright?
Just let us know when you need, Bala Hatun.
Bogac Alp! Bogac Alp!
Bogac Alp, hurry up.
-Let's go.
Praise be, my boys! Come on!
A conquest cannot be performed
only with swords, sisters.
It's performed with bread, meals and prayers.
Every ember in the fire
and every bread in the table...
...should have the
smell of conquest on them.
Right?
Come on.
Come on, my dear.
Are you helping too?
A bride is always like her
mother-in-law, they say.
It seems they are right.
Praise be.
Who are you?
Are you..
A nomad?
Yes.
I'm here to get to know Osman Bey.
Osman Bey isn't here.
He's gone to meet the emperor.
Osman Bey is powerful enough
to meet the emperor, huh?
You don't know Osman Bey, obviously.
He's the best in the frontiers.
Do you use an axe?
Can you teach me how to use it?
Tell me, double-sworded boy.
What is your name?
Ghazi Alp.
Alright. Okay.
I'll teach you, but...
...you need to tell me about
the news in the frontiers.
I will.
The fate of the frontiers
will be redetermined in Iznik.
Let's see whether this talk
will bring benefits or troubles.
My Bey.
Why do you think the emperor invited us here?
Games never end in these lands.
A new order will be provided.
Let's see which side we will take.
Allah is with us, my Bey.
The rest doesn't matter.
The precious and great city of the Roman Empire.
The ancient town of Christians
that has never been conquered.
Welcome to Nikea, Osman Bey.
Thanks for welcoming us
in the city that our ancestor
Suleyman Shah, son of
Kutalmis Bey, once conquered,
..commander.
Our mighty emperor Andronikos
is expecting you, Osman Bey.
Let's go.
Praise be, alps!
Come on, warriors! Cling your swords!
Faster.
Watch me, man.
I use double swords very well.
But I can't use an axe.
I trained a lot.
But I keep dropping it.
Tell me what my mistake is.
You hold the axe too tightly.
You shouldn't hold it
tightly but in a balanced way.
Watch me.
Praise be.
Brothers, who is that stranger swinging the axe?
I haven't seen him before
but he's good at using an axe.
Tell me, Aykurt Cavus.
Can you beat that man?
Let's see.
Uncle, what have you done?
The axe isn't only your weapon
but also your arms and wings.
If you think that way, you will never drop it.
I got it, uncle.
You are a great fighter.
Praise be.
Peace be upon you.
Peace be upon you too.
So you swing your axe well, old man.
Praising myself would be childish.
But for sure, no man
has defeated me until today.
Then come and show your bravery.
We never stayed back from practicing.
Come on, show your skills.
Come on then. In the name of Allah,
the merciful, the compassionate.
Come on brother.
Brother!
Good, good.
Hay Praise be.
Praise be.
They called you old, but you defeated two Alps.
Thanks.
Your hearts are very strong,
valiants. You fight well.
Thank you, thank you.
Tell... tell me.
What is the name of the valiant who
defeated me and dropped my mace?
An Alp who fights in the way of
glorification of the word of Allah.
That's all.
Hay Praise be.
Praise be.
Alright.
I wanted to see Osman Bey, but I
heard he went to meet the emperor.
Does anyone know why he went?
We don't know why he went.
We are also waiting for our Bey.
We will know our target when Osman Bey returns.
Osman Bey.
Seeing you coming here with peace...
I am very happy you accepted my invitation.
Coming to the West is our never ending rule.
Emperor Andronikos.
This table is prepared for you. Please, come.
Your strength is still with you like your rule.
Time treated you well. You haven't aged a bit.
Wars or the tricks of Byzantium don't tire us.
Despite the failure of
your tricks and attempts...
...even though you gave Bursa to
the Mongols with Claudius' rebellion...
...I see you are still very happy.
You are talking about the
thousands-year-old Roman Empire, Osman Bey.
Even though we made plans and sometimes
fell into traps, we always stood strong.
Because our foundations are solid.
I own half the world.
With the roads we built..
...and unique buildings like Hagia Sophia,
we brought civilization to the world.
And also, Byzantium is not
the only state that lost things.
I heard it.
The Ilkhanid Mongols took your tribe.
Even if the Turk loses...
...he never stops until he
takes back what he lost.
So, Andronikos.
My ancestors who once
spread fear in your empire...
...Cagri and Tugrul Bey, you know them well.
They lost their tribes.
The Ghaznavids and the Karakhanids...
You underestimated them.
But my ancestors' dreams were so strong that..
...you learned this in the
hardest way at Manzikert.
Since that time, the Turk's goal
and dream have never changed.
Even if we lose our tribes...
In the hardest times...
We know how to rise again.
And..
We always know how to establish a state.
Now it's not about personal
resurrection or salvation, Osman Bey.
The situation requires an alliance
for the future of the frontiers...
Byzantium and the Kayi tribe.
Emperor..
...when I saved your life, you offered me peace.
But that peace...
...only brought us betrayal.
While the Mongols are
bringing their army here...
...betrayal of the alliance would
bring disaster to the frontiers.
On the contrary...
...my wish is for this alliance, which
started for defense, to grow through trade.
We can establish a common marketplace.
We can trade without paying taxes.
Did I understand correctly?
In this region, in these frontiers..
...Kayi's growth and its development...
do not scare you?
Rome is not scared of anyone, Osman Bey.
As long as you stay loyal to the alliance
and do not wage war against the West.
If Kayi becomes strong within its own borders...
...it will also protect our eastern borders.
That Mongol, who caused us to lose Bursa
and who is served by that dog Claudius...
If you defeat Kucar, Osman Bey...
...then we will no longer be
enemies, we will be friends forever.
So, Emperor...
..you say you fear no one.
But your rebellious commander Claudius...
...you fear him.
He is a traitor.
It's not about fear, the real issue
is the wound he gave to Byzantium.
Let's say I prefer an enemy
who looks me in the eye...
...over a traitor who stabs me in the back.
You're a weak Byzantine
soldier, but not too bad.
You... You..
You are too weak to even hurt my fingernail.
Kucar, I am not your enemy.
Go and take your anger out on Osman.
Not just Osman, none of
the Muslims on this land...
...will be able to escape my wrath.
When my army arrives, no
heads will remain on shoulders!
So..
...you want me to defeat our
common enemy, the Mongols.
You say that in this way our
friendship will last forever?
In return for our friendship,
I want an army from you.
If I weren't fighting with the
Kipchaks in the Balkans...
...I would place my army on the frontiers.
But in this alliance, my duty
is to open my treasury to you...
...so you can strengthen your army.
You can't win this war with gold.
If you won't give an army...
...then you will give more than gold.
Tell me, Osman Bey.
What do you want from me
as the price of this alliance?
Along with gold...
...I want to rule the Karacabes
Castle and all the lands around it.
Karacabes Castle is one
of the lifelines of my empire.
Will you take a piece of my flesh
by using our alliance, Osman Bey?
You already lost your lifeline Bursa,
to your rebellious commander Claudius.
Now this precious city, Iznik, and the others...
Do you want to give them to the Mongols?
If not..
...then you will give me what I want.
And I will stand against the Mongols.
I will send Kucar away from these lands.
With my life and my army,
I will stand against them all.
Your rebellious commander Claudius..
When he becomes weak, you will destroy him too.
Agreed, Osman Bey.
The gold and the Karacabes Castle are yours.
You handle Kucar, and I will handle Claudius.
And I hope both our trade and
our friendship will last forever.
God willing.
God willing Emperor.
My soldiers are coming
from the borders of Enguru.
They travel quietly day and night.
Kucar..
...with your army and my
soldiers, we will rule all the frontiers.
Then we will ride our horses
to west and rule all the lands.
Exciting.
Then what?
Then..
I will dethrone that old
Emperor and sit on the throne.
I will rule Rome.
You
You will be nothing...
...more than a commander sleeping
on a throne under my shadow and...
...under the protection of the Khan
of Khans Olcaytu Khan, Claudius.
Everything is done, right? I want no mistakes.
Everything should be ready for our army.
It's as you ordered, mother. Done.
Mother, these carts are going with the others.
Bring it.
Good. Cover it.
Let me see those.
Good.
They're all going to the army camp in Karaorman.
Place the materials in the most shadowed spot.
-As you order, Bala Hatun.
-Come on.
May your work be easy, hatuns!
-Welcome, Bala Hatun.
-Thank you.
Welcome.
-Welcome.
-Are you well?
Thanks to Allah, I am.
-May your work be easy.
-We're all working.
Praise be, Praise be. May your work be easy.
The same man, mother.
He was watching us while
we were going into the woods.
But we didn't care.
He's been watching us
since we came to the tribe.
He was walking around the carts yesterday.
He may be the spy who informs Begum.
I'm sure. That's him.
First, we will follow
Let's see if he meets Begum.
I'll manage the preparations.
Girls, you follow him with the alps.
Be cautious, though.
Don't let him realize you're following.
What if he meets Begum?
You'll take that snake
and bring her to our tribe.
-As you order, mother.
Come on, girls.
Let's see where he goes.
Here is the gold that our mighty emperor
Andronikos promised you, Osman Bey.
Alps, take it.
Excuse me.
My Bey.
Forgive me.
Demanding a castle is one thing.
But going to a war with that
heathen's gold... I don't know, my Bey.
I don't feel comfortable either, my Bey.
Don't worry.
The gold is for Kucar's head.
Well... We divided Byzantine.
Kucar and Gladius will be next.
You meet Gladius.
Tell him we want to have a deal.
He should come to Akcapinar tomorrow.
Okay, my Bey.
Tell Cerkutay.
The castle of Karacabes will belong to Turks.
He should capture and then reinforce it.
As you order, my Bey
He's waiting for someone.
Shall we make him speak?
If he is Begum's spy, he must know where she is.
I don't think so.
Begum must have taken measures
in case her spy gets caught.
No doubt.
That's her spy.
She has to pay for the
things that she made us suffer.
We'll wait and see.
If it is Begum who he is waiting for,
...she won't be able to run off this time.
Many khans, many rulers...
...many commanders and soldiers, Turks have had.
Some struggled behind Tengri Mountains in Hotan.
Some, in the west, made the
enemy think he was the scourge.
Osman Bey is one of those great rulers, man.
He is a brave man who hits the cruel and all
the heathens like a scourge in the frontiers.
You must be happy that you live
under the wings of such a brave Bey.
Thank Allah.
With the guidance of Osman
Bey, the ruler in the frontiers,
...those will protect all the orphans
and the ones in need, God willing.
God willing.
Once upon a time, I was the
fellow of a courageous Bey.
The sword he lifted towards the sky
became a sun raining fire on the cruel...
...and cooled the innocent with its shadow.
He was a Bey who brought
order and justice wherever he went.
Which Bey is that?
Tell me, man.
The one who settled in
these lands with his tribe
...avoided nothing at all to make
this land a homeland for Turks,
...proved that Turks would prevail
forever against the whole world...
...and became a soldier for the Islam world.
He was Ertugrul Ghazi.
Ertugrul Ghazi.
-He said Ertugrul Ghazi.
-Ertugrul Ghazi.
What does this old man say, brothers?
Were you one of the soldiers of
Ertugrul Ghazi, Osman Bey's father?
Osman Bey.
What's going on here?
Who are you? Show me your face.
How?
How is that possible?
Turgut Ghazi.
Yes.
Tell me, Osman Bey.
Do you have a place in your tribe...
...and in your army for this alp?
What are you even saying?
This tribe, tent and army is already yours.
Welcome, Turgut Ghazi.
Thank you, good to see you.
Praise be.
Praise be...
My father's fellow.
-Turgut Ghazi, the bravest of the brave!
-Thank you, Osman Bey. Thank you.
Come with me.
The person you see, my children.
...is Turgut Ghazi who suffered a lot for Kayi.
Sisters, prepare a tent for
him and show great respect.
You are the man with whose
brave stories we grew up, huh?
Turgut Ghazi, whose axe fought together
with Bamsi Bey's double swords, huh?
Right.
Well... My son Orhan. My son Alaaddin.
Praise be.
Ertugrul Bey's family have grown bigger.
Praise be, boys.
The preparation made for the army has set out.
They're going to keep it in a
hidden camp in Karaorman.
Karaorman, huh?
All their preparation will go for nothing.
Their army won't be able
to have anything to eat.
Alps, get ready. We're going to Karaorman.
Vural, go back to their tribe
and let me know their every step.
Alps, watch out.
It's time to pay for what you did, Begum.
You all have come to me to pass away, huh?
Alps, attack!
Halime, protect yourself.
Begum
You will pay, Begum.
You will pay for everything.
I did everything because
of the injustice I suffered.
You thought you could run off?
You attempted to...
You attempted to burn my mother alive.
You attempted to burn my mother alive, huh?
I will kill you. I'll kill you.
-I will kill you.
-Fatma. Fatma!
-I'll kill you!
-Fatma, stop that!
-Let me kill her.
-Fatma, stop!
Let her kill. She deserves to die.
-I will kill her.
-Fatma!
It's mother and father who deserve to kill her.
Will you really take it from them?
Sisters, tie her up!
We're taking her to our tribe.
Come on. Let's go.
This sword...
With my brothers Bamsi and Dogan...
...we always...
...rode to the blessed
destinations this sword showed.
The owner of this sword
taught us the faith, my Osman.
May my Ertugrul Bey rest in heaven...
This generation owes you so much.
Our generation owes you and
the many valiants you mentioned.
Ha, Turgut Ghazi?
Thank you.
Tell me.
Where have you been all this time?
What did you do?
We thought you passed
away from this mortal world.
Tell me.
I was in the Balkans.
I brought you the respect and
greetings of many Turks who settled there.
They are waiting to hear your horse's footsteps.
They are all waiting for you.
Tell me. What did you do in those lands?
My Ertugrul Bey gave me a secret
duty, that's why I had to disappear.
I was there for that duty.
I was a companion to Saru Saltuk for years.
We kept struggling and
working for the cause of Islam.
My wise father.
Even while fighting in the fire
circle, he did not forget the Balkans.
Now my last wish is to...
...dedicate the rest
of my life to the path of
Osman Bey, who fights
in the fire like his father.
You will be a mountain behind
me like you were for my father, huh?
For sure.
Hay Praise be.
My uncle, the legacy of my father.
Thank you my Osman. Thank you.
You will be nothing...
...more than a commander sleeping
on a throne under my shadow and...
...under the protection of the Khan
of Khans Olcaytu Khan, Claudius.
So I am under your shadow, Kucar?
You dirty pedicular pig of the steppe.
I will use everyone and
everything until I don't need them.
You will pay for this, Kucar.
My rule you thought was under
your shadow will be your end.
Walk!
Walk Begum!
Traitor!
Walk!
Begum...
You snake... So it was you, huh?
Come here!
Do you remember?
You tried to imprison me in my own tribe.
I told you that day you
would go where you deserved!
Now that day has come, Begum! Get up!
I told you, you can not take anything from me.
You tried to kill me and
made my children suffer.
Get up
Stop it!
Get up Begum, get up!
This is for the cruelty you did to my people!
This is for attempting to hurt my children!
Get up!
Stop it!
And this is because you
set your eyes on my family!
Get up! Get up Begum!
Do not disgrace me here Bala!
You are already a disgrace!
Kill me! Kill me already!
Don't worry, the end you deserve will come.
Attention
Osman Bey!
My Bey
My Bey, forgive me!
Forgive me, my Bey!
I regret it, my Bey!
Please, forgive me!
You liar...
Bring her into the tent.
Commander Claudius...
Master Claudius is listening to you.
The ruler of Yenisehir, Sogut,
Karacahisar, Atranos, Lefke,
Karadin and Akhisar, the sun
of the frontiers and of all Turks...
I heard enough.
Doesn't it scare you that I can kill you?
I am here by the order of the ruler
Osman Bey, protector of all Turkmens.
And the answer of your question, Commander.
Since I am wearing my
faith in Allah like armor...
I am never afraid of death.
That happens to faithless people like you.
You Turks mistake ignorance
of barbarism for courage.
What a pity...
If I want to..
...I can put my hand inside your
chest and take your heart out.
But I don't want to do that.
Why?
First, your cities that you
love so much will burn.
In flames.
While they burn, your
people will scream and shout.
You will see this first.
You will be afraid.
Then you will die.
Tell me..
What does Osman want from me?
Osman Bey...
...wants to meet with you...
...tomorrow in the Akcapinar
to make an agreement.
An agreement?
War is coming.
Osman will die anyway.
Why would I agree?
How do you know that fate won't bring
new victory to the Turks, Commander?
My Osman Bey wants to make a
beneficial agreement for everyone.
Tell Osman I will come.
Let's meet then, Osman Bey.
Let's meet.
My Bey.
What are we going to discuss? She
is a traitor. Isn't her punishment death?
My Osman Bey.
Forgive me.
I made a mistake because of my anger and pride.
Forgive me, my Bey.
Anger and pride, huh?
You united with the enemy,
Begum. You tried to hurt my children.
I am saying that I regret it, Bala Hatun.
I know there's no forgiveness for
what I did. But please show mercy.
Osman Bey.
Did you never think before betraying us?
But the fear of death.
When it comes...
My eyes were blind to the truth, my Bey.
Your brother
What about your brother?
He fought bravely and became a martyr.
Allow me. Allow me to make up for it, my Bey.
Let me die in a way that
befits my brother and my name.
You didn't come here
after feeling regret, Begum.
You were caught while you were making a
treacherous move. Don't you have shame?
I don't want to die, Bala Hatun.
I will do whatever you say.
So...
...you will do whatever we want, huh?
Whatever you want, my Bey. Just don't kill me.
I will give you a chance to save your life.
Listen to me carefully.
You came to see my dead body. But I am not dead.
Shut up. My father must have a plan about you.
Don't get happy, Begum. As long as you have
this greed, you will make more mistakes.
And then, we will take
your life without hesitation.
I have learned my lesson,
Hatuns. I won't make mistakes.
We will see. From now on,
we will always be watching you.
Look at this little traitor.
What did you say? Shut up.
Who do you call a traitor?
Don't make me kill you here!
Fatma. Fatma.
We are leaving.
I might be mad, but we are family.
Don't look at me like that.
What am I going to do now?
O the Owner of the skies and the earth.
O my Allah, the Most Glorious.
The most Merciful of the merciful.
My Allah..
May You forgive all my sins, past and present.
Do not separate me from the
path of the Prophets, my Allah.
O my Allah, the Most Glorious.
Do not withhold Your help from us.
Make every step we take for Your cause firm.
May You give strength to my
state, my people, and my army.
Do not separate me and my descendants
from Your cause and Your path, my Allah.
May You grant us victory over our enemies.
Aameen.
Can I come in, my Bey?
Come in Boran.
My Bey, Claudius has agreed to meet.
Alright then. Make the preparations.
As you order my Bey.
Bala.
My Bey.
Claudius accepted the meeting.
We sent Begum with Aykurt before the sunrise.
I didn't take her life.
For our state, her living self is
more valuable than her dead body.
My father Koca Bey did the right thing by
pledging allegiance to Osman Bey, uncle.
The valiants who'll be raised here,
the Ergenekon of Turks...
...will strike the enemy's chest like a ram.
The man holds the sword,
the Bey says the word, Oguz.
I fear that these glorious valiants
will die under Osman's command.
Uncle, what do you mean?
Having the state which settled in
the hearts of Turks is our right, Oguz.
Ah uncle..
I hope my father does not
hear these words of yours.
It was my grandmother's heirloom. It should
be somewhere around here. Let's find it.
Is this yours, Kayi girl?
Why do you have it?
I don't know. You tell me.
Give it to me.
Are Kayi girls always this angry?
Angry? Who are you for
me to get angry at you, huh?
I said give it to me, or else...
Or else what?
Is this the reward for my favor, Kayi girl?
Favor? I am the one who is doing you a favor.
Despite your madness,
I can still control myself.
Don't make me hurt you here. Go now.
Who is he? Do you know him?
I don't need to know him.
Considering he dared to talk to me like that,
...he must be a madman.
A madman who lost his mind.
Maybe, he lost his mind when he saw you.
Halime.
I say what I see, Fatma Hatun.
Move.
Osman Bey is up to something again.
We'll see.
In the name of Allah, the most
merciful, the most compassionate.
-Brother.
-Father.
My boy.
My nephew wanted to come
immediately when you called us, brother.
Turks are struggling for
their existence, my Bey.
I wanted to join you during this tough fight.
Well thought, my boy. We need
every man in this tough fight.
What is the preparation
in the tribe for, my brother?
Does it have anything to
do with you inviting me here?
Tell the alps to be ready, Yigit.
Why? A fight?
Against whom?
Wait.
We'll talk after the council.
After the council.
-Peace be upon you.
-Peace be upon you too.
Ertugrul Ghazi's brave fellow.
We've heard your name a lot.
Welcome.
Thank you, Koca Bey. Live long.
Attention, Osman Bey!
-Peace be upon you.
-Peace be upon you too.
Peace be upon you too.
I invited you.
And you came quickly. Thank you.
The council which is being held here today...
...will determine the
fate of Kayi and all Turks.
As you know
...the order and balance in the
frontiers keep changing all the time.
Yet we, who follow the right
path, will bring the true order.
They say the heathen emperor
gave you a cart of gold, Osman Bey.
We've all heard that.
Those men do nothing but evil.
What order do they want to bring now?
We didn't take only the
gold but also their castle.
According to the deal between
me and Emperor Andronikos,
...with no bloodshed and no martyrs,
...we took the castle of Karacabes for Turks.
Karacabes, huh?
It's the most important castle which
opens the way to Bursa in the west.
Yes, the most important.
For this reason, the order in Karacabes
should be maintained in no time.
Well..
If Claudius thinks that it's
going to be threat against Bursa...
...when he learns that we captured the castle
...he will certainly attempt
to make a move against us.
The duty of ruling and reinforcing Karacabes...
...is yours, Orhan Bey.
Cerkutay has gone to take over the castle.
From now on, you will live there with your wife.
As you order, my Bey.
Excuse me, my Bey. I
should go make preparations.
Of course, of course.
The heathens gave us the gift of
Karacabes in return for what, my Bey?
I don't understand.
Stopping the Mongolian army
while they come to our lands...
...is an inevitable fight to protect our state.
But there is one thing the emperor doesn't know.
With the gold he gave us,
we will divide our enemies.
Do you know what this letter means?
You don't.
This letter means you will..
...surrender this castle...
...unconditionally without a resistance.
Alps!
Show these soldiers the door.
And make sure that they have all left.
Come on.
Put those rags down.
Hang our glorious banners instead.
The whole world should know
that Osman Bey took this castle...
...without swords but with politics.
With the gold the emperor gave you,
you'll both make Claudius be your ally...
...and separate him from Kucar...
...and make him leave his nest with the news...
..and take his head.
Is that right, my Bey?
They will think we are making a mistake.
But it will be them who
makes the biggest mistake.
What about the Mongolian army?
They're marching from the
east to the west sneakily.
What is our target?
According to the information we got.
...the Mongolian army will pass
through here and come to our borders.
We don't know which route they will follow next.
But we'll put them in the route we want.
How will that be possible, my Bey?
An army can march with no food.
But without water, they can't walk.
For this reason, we will make all
the water wells in this area unusable.
We'll only leave this area available for them.
-Camlica region, my Bey.
-Camlica region.
Streams and the cliffs there.
They will pass through them.
And they will fall into our trap.
Brilliant idea.
They aren't our equals, but...
...we and the heathens
are in equal conditions now.
I'm ready for this mission.
Okay, okay.
Well..
Turgut Ghazi.
-Alaaddin.
-My Bey.
And Turahan.
It's your duty to break Mongolians.
-As you order, my Bey.
Okay.
And you, Turahan.
You won't let even a single
soldier come from the east.
With the alps you take
...this duty is yours.
You'll be the border commander of the frontiers.
I'd sacrifice my life for Islam, my Bey.
I swear I will carry out this
duty with my life and blood.
Thank you, thank you.
Turgut Ghazi, my father's fellow.
You beat my alps during the training, huh?
Your alps are well trained.
But we need to train the young ones.
I want you to train the alps.
You have trained many men
and broken many bones, huh?
Your wish is my command.
I'll carry out the duty.
Thank you, thank you.
Here we go.
Everybody knows their duties.
It's time for fight.
Yes, my Bey!
What decision did the council give, brother?
Against whom will we send all those alps?
Kucar, Orlok of Mongolians, who dishonors
the frontiers with every step he takes.
We'll march towards that dog's
armies marching to the frontiers.
We'll beat and destroy
all of them, with Allah's will.
You'll stay here, Oghuz.
They need Beys and soldiers here too, right?
My brave son!
Osman Bey.
He's going to beat Kucar, huh?
Attention, Osman Bey!
O people!
My Beys! My alps!
You, who sacrificed a lot for the sake
of Allah and for the glory of our state!
The council is over.
Now it's time for fight.
Long live Osman Bey!
Some betrayed us.
Some brought troubles from distant places!
But they all intended to
capture and destroy Turks.
I'm asking you.
Will we let that happen?
Never! Never, my Bey!
Of course not.
Those fools are reaching out to
harm our existence and freedom!
Well... The warriors of the Prophet's.
Brave fighters!
Don't get your heads down
because we are outnumbered!
Don't encourage the ones
who are happy to outnumber us!
Our faith melting the iron mountains...
...will destroy all of them!
This sword is a weapon to them.
But it's a brother to us.
Death scaring them is a fabulous feast to us!
They can't be martyrs or ghazis. Only we can!
What will make us victorious is
the blood shed for the sake of Allah!
Allah is the greatest!
Allah is the greatest! Allah is the greatest!
-Allah is the greatest!
I seek refuge in Allah from the accursed satan
In the name of Allah,
the most compassionate, the most merciful.
Truly We have opened up a path to
clear triumph for you [Prophet],
so that God may forgive you
your past and future sins
complete His grace upon you,
guide you to a straight path,
and help you mightily.
It was He who made His tranquillity
descend into the hearts of the believers
o add faith to their faith, the forces
of the heavens and earth belong to God;
He is all knowing and all wise
so as to admit believing men and women into
Gardens graced with flowing streams
there to remain, absolving their bad deeds
a great triumph in God’s eyes
and to torment the hypocritical and idolatrous men
and women who harbour evil thoughts about God
it is they who will be encircled by evil!
who carry the burden of God’s anger
whom God has rejected and for whom
He has prepared Hell, an evil destination!
The forces of heaven and earth belong to God;
He is almighty and all wise.
We have sent you [Prophet] to bring
good news and to give warning,
so that you[people] may believe in God and His Messenger
support Him, honour Him, and praise Him morning and evening.
Will we trust Osman, sir?
I trust nobody but myself.
Wait in the woods with your best men.
Come here. Come.
Osman... Let's see what you
will promise to convince me.
Our army will come soon.
What will Osman's first move be, Kucar?
Osman will surely make a move.
He doesn't know where our army is but...
...he will poison all the wells on the border.
Osman will not risk the innocent
people's lives by doing this.
He will find a solution for that.
We need to make a move to prevent this.
We already did.
No one will drink water
before taking precautions.
If the wells are poisoned, our army...
...will come through the valleys
from Camlica, between the streams.
This way, they will both
be able to drink water...
...and move forward without being noticed.
This is such poison that even a
single drop will destroy a person.
In the name of Allah,
the most merciful, the most compassionate.
They will either control
the wells or drink and die.
Both paths lead to our victory.
If they notice the poison...
...they will turn their way towards the Camlica.
Now we will wait.
They will die either by poison or by the sword.
We will send them away like
sending dogs away, my Shahzade.
The cost of invading our lands is
bleeding to death. Everyone will see.
They will.
Alps, poison all the wells, troughs,
and water bodies in the area.
Lay in ambush.
Do not let the people approach the
places you have poisoned for a while. Go!
Come on.
Come, Hatun, come.
Share my food with me.
Take this.
Eat it.
Thank you Kucar.
I brought you important news.
Tell me.
My spy in the tribe heard it.
That Claudius that you trust so much...
...is allies with Osman.
What are you saying, Hatun?
They are going to meet in Akcapinar.
It is time to cut the heads of these two devils.
Mankurt.
Go and check if this
Hatun is telling the truth!
I'll come after you! Go!
You wait, Hatun.
...you are not telling me the
truth, I will skin you Hatun!
That demon is walking around.
And he got really mad.
It is the order of my Osman Bey.
If you are playing a game, I will
kill you here with my own hands.
Why would I come with you
if I wanted to play a game?
I am just warning you.
Alps, we are returning to the tribe. Come on!
Those are Mongol scouts, my Shahzade.
Draw water from the well!
They took the bait!
They will give that water to their horses...
But the horses won't drink that
water. They will sense the poison.
Two heads are better than one, my Shahzade.
They will escape from the
poison but get caught by the sword.
God willing. God willing.
Orlok Kucar is right.
The water is poisoned.
We will inform the Commander
of the army. Come on!
There is no way for them to pass
through here to reach the water channels.
They will fall into our trap... Then...
...the soil will be watered with Mongol blood.
Wait here.
Osman.
What happened?
Did we come here to
celebrate my victory in Bursa?
I came to remove those chains from your neck.
Chains?
I guess I came here to listen to
your ridiculous words, is that it?
I am talking about the chains on your neck.
The chain Kucar put around your neck.
Now you're really starting to talk nonsense.
-You know we're talking about my ally, right?
-He's not your ally.
Kucar is your owner.
And we both know that.
Now..
if you want Bursa...
...you have to get rid of Kucar.
You said we would fight against Kucar, brother.
What is Osman Bey doing with that infidel now?
His intention is to set the
dogs against each other,
divide his enemies, and
swallow them one by one.
Then..
...how are we going to get rid of Kucar?
Osman..
I asked you. How are we
going to get rid of Kucar?
Come on!
What are you going to do?
Will you give this gold and
tell Kucar to leave Bursa?
This is your share of the gold.
I mean... Your price.
Price?
While I am fighting with Kucar...
...you won't join a side.
I will rip him and his army out of these lands.
And you..
...will be the only ruler of Bursa.
Well, well
I always said that you are a smart man Osman.
What's going to happen now?
You will keep me away from this fight.
You will win a victory against
Kucar without any losses.
Then what will happen?
Who's next?
Me?
This won't be a battle without losses.
We will lose our men and get hurt.
But I don't want to make a move while injured.
I also don't want anyone
coming at me while I'm hurt.
That s why
...I want this gold...
...to be the symbol of peace between us...
...in the alliance we make against Kucar.
Alright then.
But our enmity remains. Right?
Our enmity will last until one of us dies.
Good
Before killing Kucar, tell
him how much I sold him for.
I don't want him to think he was cheap.
What Begum said is true.
Osman and Claudius made an
alliance. They will make peace and trade.
Claudius..
If I don't burn you in the flames...
...may they not call me Kucar.
Osman gave a cart full
of gold for this alliance.
Their alliance is now definite.
To teach everyone a lesson, I will
skin Claudius in the middle of Bursa.
Let's go! Come on!
We have put the Mongols on our path.
Now, they will become our prey.
And that fool Kucar is not with them.
They will never come together
as well. Our plan worked.
Osman Bey was right again.
May Allah grant us another victory.
May He grant us another one, God willing.
God willing.
I was destined to fight next to
my grandfather's companion.
Thanks to my Allah..
Thanks to my Allah, Alaeddin Ali. Thanks to Him.
From now on, neither arrows nor
spears will be able to defeat me.
Seeing that the family
of Ertugrul Bey, may his
place be heaven, have
grown like a plane tree,
...I'd die with pleasure.
Just wait, Turgut Ghazi. Just wait, old man.
There are many bones and walls to break.
Alright.
But now it's time to
slaughter those blood suckers!
Come on. We need to go.
Osman!
Well..
You will beg for mercy. I will take your life!
I'd rather I could kill Claudius who
betrayed me by holding your hand, but...
...I have to kill you first, Osman.
Kill me? No.
Who could even have a
more terrible fate than you?
What unbreakable courage you have, Osman!
You lost your tribe against a troop of nokers.
You think you can win against my armies?
You rely on your army?
Tell me then. Where is your
army now? What are they doing?
What are you talking about?
Speak clearly.
Shahzades you were trying to capture.
They are busy destroying your army right now.
And my part is killing a demon like you.
You think you can destroy my armies?
I'm not only ruining your armies...
...but also all your plans against
my state, nation and family!
Well... Today,
...you're going deep under the ground.
Archers, now!
In the name of Allah.
Come on, alps!
Until nokers, who are our
enemies, die! Allah is the greatest!
Allah is the greatest!
-Come on, brothers!
-In the name of Allah!
Allah is the greatest!
Osman Bey's alps.
Osman Bey was always right.
We made a mistake. Now it's
time to make up for our mistake.
Come on, come on!
Come on!
We're here for help, warriors! Allah is the greatest!
Thank you, valiant. You are
a great fighter, Praise be.
Thank you, Turgut Ghazi.
Come on, brothers!
Allah is the greatest!
The Righteous!
I've seen many tongueless dogs like you.
I've always killed you with my sword of justice.
-Nokers!
-Here we go.
You heathen dog.
Where are you going?
I'm talking to you. Where are you going?
Look at me.
Your time is over, Kucar.
Your evil actions cannot be covered now.
You'll pay for what you did.
Allah is the greatest!
-Victory is ours!
-Allah is the greatest!
Allah is the greatest! Allah is the greatest!
Hasan Bey.
You had abandoned the tribe.
Tell me now. Why did you come for help?
I was blind. Alaaddin Bey.
I couldn't see the truth.
But then I realized that Osman
Bey's path was the straight path.
Many Beys and alps made the same mistake.
But realizing your mistake
is a virtue, Hasan Bey.
It is. It is but...
..I can't look at Osman Bey's face anymore.
Have a safe path. I will go my own way.
Oghuzs must be one body, boy.
If we get separated, we
will give the enemy a chance.
Obviously, Hasan Bey regrets what he did.
We should let Osman Bey know this.
I thought you were smart, Osman.
But you are a fool too.
You made a lot of mistakes
and are kneeling before me now.
You fell into my trap.
Trap? What are you talking about?
Claudius.
-The deal I made with Claudius.
-What are you talking about, Osman?
-Speak clearly!
-Who brought you the information?
Begum.
Yes, Begum.
Begum!
Begum, of course.
Have your never doubted?
You thought the one who betrayed
her state and nation wouldn't betray you?
In return for gold, I got your
deal with Claudius canceled.
And with the information,
you became a prey for me.
What about my armies?
How did you...
We didn't poison the
wells to kill your soldiers...
...but to make them go
near the river in despair.
You think you can overcome Mongolians...
...by killing me and breaking my
armies marching to the frontiers?
Every army you break and every life you take...
...will come back as a bigger trouble, Osman.
Come! You can all come!
Look at me.
Since I first saw you
...my sword has always been bloodthirsty.
It's time for you to die now.
Mongolians never bleed, Osman.
Mongolian soldiers flow like a flood.
And you will drown in that flood, Osman.
You say so?
If you are a flood, we become a dam.
If you are an avalanche, we become a mountain.
Whatever you
...we will always be against you.
Now...
Now your time is over.
I swear on my sword painted red with blood!
Whoever dishonors the right
religion Islam and the glory of Turks...
...will always lie on the
ground like this corpse!
Allah is the greatest!
-Allah is the greatest!
Good.
Praise be, sisters. Praise be.
Our raids have restarted.
We have to be ready for duties.
Never stop training.
As you order, Bala Hatun!
It's your turn, Halime Hatun.
Show me your skills.
As you order, mother.
Praise be.
-You're good.
-Not at all, mother.
I dropped my sword.
You were fighting against
Bala Hatun, the head of Sisters.
I'm not like anyone else, dear.
Fatma, Halime should keep training with Sisters.
However agile she is, she must be trained by us.
Don't worry, mother.
I will trained her well.
-Bala Hatun.
-Come.
That snake woman insists on not eating anything.
-She has never left the tent.
-She shouldn't.
The less she walks around, the better it is.
Mother, but...
If she doesn't eat anything, she will fall weak.
I'll take food to her with your permission.
Do it.
But be careful, dear.
Although she protected
your life, she is our enemy.
Come on.
She is merciful like you.
God willing, this mercy will
not cause us trouble, Ulgen.
God willing.
I made delicious sherbet,
would you like to drink some?
Yes, I would.
You should hold your sword stronger.
Sisters, you continue. Come on.
What are you doing here, huh?
Don't you hear me? I am
talking to you, are you deaf?
Are you talking to me?
No.
I'm talking to the axe over there.
You both sound the same anyway!
You recognized me quickly, Kayi girl.
I am as strong as an axe.
I can defeat anyone I strike with my sword.
Who are you? Are you an Alp?
It's clear you're new.
If you're not afraid of being
defeated, practice with me.
But if you manage to drop my sword, Kayi girl...
..I'll tell you who I am.
I don't practice with everyone.
Especially not with a madman like you.
Go and leave me alone.
Or just tell me you are scared.
Give me patience, Allah!
Are you really crazy?
What are you saying?
Do you want to die? Don't you know who she is?
Who is she?
I feel sorry for you.
You were a good Alp. But your time is up.
The Hatun you just said was scared is
Osman Bey's daughter, Fatma Hatun.
Now, calculate what's going to happen.
Yes, calculate, but don't go over the limit!
Osman Bey's daughter Fatma Hatun?
What am I doing here?
Damn you, Claudius.
Because of you, I lost everything.
I said I am not going to eat your food.
Why don't you understand?
You haven't eaten anything.
You're sick. You need to eat.
Poena.
My little bird.
Do you care about me like before?
My name is Halime.
I just...
I don't want to owe you anything.
You don't owe me anything.
Look at our situation.
I lost you, I lost Bursa I have nothing left.
Look at this.
Poena.
I raised you for ten years.
My little bird.
This is not you.
You threw me into darkness.
I found peace with Islam.
This is me, Sofia.
I am Halime.
And I...
Thank Allah, I am Muslim.
Poena..
Damn it..
-Osman Bey welcome!
-Thank you!
Thank you.
Welcome my Bey!
Thank you, thank you.
We heard the enemies lost and faced defeat.
May your victory be blessed, my Bey. Welcome.
Thank you, Bala. Thank you.
Make preparations. We will
celebrate this with a feast.
As you order.
Come on Hatuns. Prepare the meals. Set the fire.
Let's go. Sisters. Come on!
The enemies of Islam in the frontiers
have been punished by your sword, my Bey.
Thank you.
In the frontiers, you
kept the light of Islam eternal...
...and destroyed the
dogs of the devil, my Bey.
Thank you!
May Allah grant you a long life, my Bey.
May your state be everlasting.
Thank you
Thank you, live long.
Peace be upon you.
Peace be upon you too.
Where is Sofia, Bala?
She is in her tent, my Bey.
She hasn't come out all day.
I will talk to her.
Let's see what happens now...
-Yigit.
-Brother.
Set out immediately and
bring our people to the feast.
Bring them here, so that
they can witness our victory.
As you order, brother.
My brave son...
My brave Oguz son, like his name.
Osman Bey.
What is happening? No
one is telling me anything!
Kucar died.
His army is destroyed.
What?
How did that happen?
It was not difficult.
I made an agreement with Claudius.
And I destroyed Kucar's army.
How did you manage that?
With the gold of the
Emperor, I ruined their alliance.
Now..
...Claudius...
...is the only ruler of Bursa.
And he is the only enemy of the Emperor.
...you left the Emperor and
Claudius alone to face each other.
You divided Byzantium.
You really surprised me greatly, Osman Bey.
I mean...
...it's a smart plan.
What is it?
Are you the only one who
knows how to play games, huh?
Of course we know how to play games.
But you..
...not only like playing games against
your enemies, but also against each other.
Now you don't have an army in Bursa.
What will you do now?
By making an agreement with my enemy Claudius...
...you betrayed me, Osman Bey!
Your own people betrayed you.
You are still in my tribe.
You are still alive.
I am loyal to our agreement.
You killed Kucar.
You won.
What about me?
Me, Osman Bey...
I lost Bursa!
What was going to happen?!
Was I supposed to give Bursa
to you on a golden platter?
Look at me!
You protected my daughter.
Therefore...
You will stay here as a
guest for a while longer.
You no longer...
...have a state...
...or an army that will fight for you.
Now go and build yourself a new life.
Come on sisters! Come on!
It will get dark soon.
Come on, there's a lot to do.
Kismet!
You are quite fast while fighting, sister.
Come on! Come on! Everyone hurry up!
Let me see that..
Don't run away!
What is this?
Put some more molasses in this.
Put another jug of molasses in it. Ghazi!
Don't wander around!
I am playing a game, mother!
Do you have to play right here, my son?
Let them play, Ulgen. Let them.
Ghazi, take it, my son.
Thank you Bala Hatun.
Look at him..
May it be easy Hatuns.
Thank you.
Let me see the keshkek meal.
Let me check.
Keshkek will be done soon.
Ulgen, make the fire stronger.
Right away, my Bala.
Here, sister.
Is it good?
We've cooked the halva, after adding
some more molasses it'll be ready.
Thanks to your hands.
Thank you.
Add plenty, we must have more than we
need or it won't be enough for everyone.
Give everyone plenty of these meals.
On this blessed day, let's
make sure we all enjoy the meals.
Good.
Make sure everything is complete. Come on!
Come on sisters!
Good, good, sister. Praise be.
No troubles happened, Bala Hatun.
I carried out my duty, Bala Hatun.
What will you do to me now?
Kill me?
Your soul is so evil..
...that you don't believe we
will keep our promise, do you?
You think we will act like you.
-I am...
You're the victim of your ambitions, Begum.
You wanted to take what wasn't yours.
Your eyes, soul and heart were blind.
You spoke of death, but no.
Death isn't your punishment.
Your biggest punishment is...
...drifting away without roots
and traditions like a withered leaf.
Now get out of my tribe.
And never come back.
Get out of my sight!
Get out!
Stop!
Commander Claudius wants to see you.
I have nothing to do with Byzantine heathens.
You had things to do with Kucar, though!
Do you think I don't know you were serving him?
Me?
Yes, you.
I'll offer you two options.
To be able to survive you will serve me.
Or I will go tell Osman about
how you served Kucar like a dog.
Whichever you prefer.
Your choice.
I think he knows who you are now.
You sent a message and I came.
I came but...
I can't look at your face, my Bey.
I couldn't see the truth back then.
The deal you made with Sofia..
...was in favor of Turks.
Although you failed to see then
...you understand now, Hasan.
Right, Turgut Ghazi?
He does.
He saved us in a hard time.
The concept called a state...
...both should punish mistakes...
...and reward the loyalty.
Obviously, you regret what you did.
I'm pardoning you.
But you should know this.
You can't make such a mistake again.
Long live with your state, Osman Bey.
Long live.
Thank you.
Attention, Osman Bey!
Brave soldiers of Kayi! Courageous Beys!
With Almighty Allah's will
and your faith and efforts,
...we stood strong against the heathens again.
And we didn't let dishonor
Allah's name, Thank Allah!
-Thank Allah!
The Mongolian army and
their traps couldn't stop us.
Kucar and his army got ruined!
Allah is the greatest! Allah is the greatest!
We'll conquer the world with justice and mercy.
On all the banners we raise.
...there will be the oppressed's prayers
and the orphan's smiles beside our names.
You should also know this.
This victory isn't only
an ordinary fight for Kayi.
This victory is the footsteps...
...of a great state which
will be a homeland for the
oppressed and spread
fear in the heart of the cruel!
We will never stop.
The conquest is from us and
the victory is only from Allah!
Long live Osman Bey! Long live
Osman Bey! Long live Osman Bey!
Be seated.
Enjoy your meal. In the name of Allah,
the most compassionate, the most merciful.
-Here.
-Thank you, my Bey.
In the name of Allah,
the most compassionate, the most merciful.
Here, daughter.
Well..
A bard's tongue is as swift
as a horse's foot, they say.
Boran.
Play your kopuz!
As you order, my Bey
We are bound in heart...
...with this land...
...let's line together...
...and hold hands like a mountain.
We are bound in heart...
...with this land...
...let's line together...
...and hold hands like a mountain...
Come sister, come brother.
Let's be one, be one fist.
May its heart not be scarred
may this land never be divided.
Come sister, come brother.
Let's be one, be one fist.
May its heart not be scarred
may this land never be divided.
Live, live, live along my people!
We won't kneel even if we die...
Even when we're in trouble.
I love how diligent...
...my heroic people are...
We won't kneel even if we die...
Even when we're in trouble.
I love how diligent...
...my heroic people are...
You can't defeat a Turk's arm.
Turks' power is limitless.
Once the flag is risen...
It won't fall again.
You can't defeat a Turk's arm.
Turks' power is limitless.
Once the flag is risen...
It won't fall again.
Live, live, live along my people!
O Praise be!